ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 11, November 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 9, September 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 7, July 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol.3 No. 6, June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 5, May 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No.4, April 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No. 3, March 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No.2, February 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 3 No.1, January 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 11, November 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 10, October 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 9, September 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vo. 4 No. 7, July 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 6, June 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 5, May 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 4, April 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 3, March 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 2, February 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol.5 No. 10/11, October/November 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 5, No.8/9, August/ September 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 5, No 6/7, June/July 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 5 No.4/5, April/May1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 5 No.2/3, February/March 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 4 No.12/ Vol.5 No. 1, December 1993/ January 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 5 No.12/Vol. 6 No. 1, December 1994-March 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 6 No. 4, April 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Asian- American Free Labor Institute. Vol. 6 No. 5, May 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The CFL, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By Chinese Federation of Labour. January 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: KRIC Monthly Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Korea Labour. Issue 2, October 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: KRIC Monthly Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Korea Labour. Issue 4, December 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: FKTU News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Federation of Korean Trade Unions. No. 110, June-August 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: FKTU News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Federation of Korean Trade Unions. No. 111, September 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Guideline for FKTU Movement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Federation of Korean Trade Unions. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Outline of FKTWU, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Federation of Korean Trade Unions. Item is in English; Chinese.
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Korea's Economic Development, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Economic Planning Board. June 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor Movement in Korea, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By Hun-Ki Lee. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A New Industrial Relations System for Social Justice and Democracy in Korea, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    25-26 March 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Korea's Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Volume 10. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Afghanistan-A Shattered Country, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By International Rescue Committee. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Out of Tyranny, Isolation, and Poverty, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    By Robert Gabor; Randall C. Garton; Stacey Heath. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Contacto, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    By Federacion Argentina de Trabajadores de Luz Y Fuerza. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: SOIVA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    By Sindicato Obrero de la Industria del Vestido y Afines. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Tribuna 21, El siglo es hoy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    By Union de Obreros y Empleados Plasticos. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hidden Cost of Fashion, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    By Textile, Clothing & Footwear Union of Australia. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 41st Annual Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    By Barbados' Workers' Union. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: ABVVFGTB, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    By Belgian Trade Union Movement. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Guide Pratique, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    By Commissariat General a la Promotion du Travail. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Vademecum Securite et Hygiene, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    By FGTB. Item is in French.
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Educacao Para Todos, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    By Unicef. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 2: Elas Nao Brincam em Servico, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    By Crinacas e Adolescentes No Trabalho. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 3: GGT, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    By Central Geral dos Trabalhadores. Item is in Portuguese.
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Privatisation in Bulgaria, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    By Privatisation Agency. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report on ITGLWF Fact-Finding Mission to Bulgaria, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    By Itschert & Briones. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Cambodia and the Dilemmas of U.S. Policy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    By Brown, Frederick. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Batir la Solidarite, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Ca S'adresse a Vous, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Le Monde Ouvrier, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Box: 4, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: !Por un Chile sin Violencia!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    By Central Democratica de Trabajadores. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Informativo Contevech, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Le Plebiscite du 5 Octobre 1988 au Chili, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    By Centre International de Solidarite Ouvriere. Item is in French.
  - Item 4: Posicion de la C.D.T. Frente a la Concertacion y el Pacto Social, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    By Depto. De Difusion. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 4, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    By Sindicato de Trabajadores Manhattan de Colombia Ltda. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 4, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Cyprus: Trade Unions & Development, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    By Robinson, Donald. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Czechoslovakia on the Road to Reform, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    By Task Force on Czechoslovakia. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Reglamento, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    By Confederacion Nacional de Trabajadores Dominicanos. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: XI Congreso: Retos del Sindicalismo para el Ano 2000, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Box: 4, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Boletin Internacional de Fenastras, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    By El Salvadore. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Critical Choices, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: El Salvador: Peaceful Revolution or Armed Struggle?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Principios De Lucha Del Comite Feminino De Fenastras, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Box: 4, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labour Relations in Finland, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    By Committee For Labour Relations. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Droit Sur L'Egalite, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Syndicalisme. Item is in French.
  - Item 2: Les Etudes Sociales et Syndicales, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By France. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: L'Integration En Marche, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By CFDT Magazine. Item is in French.
- Box: 4, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Breves D'Europe Et Nouvelles Du Monde, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
    By Force Ouvriere. Item is in French.
  - Item 2: La Clause Sociale, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: La Loi Quinquennale Sur L'Emploi, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: L'Ecole Publique En Danger, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Box: 4, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.2 (1991:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.1 (1991:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.6 (1992:Autumn). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.5 (1992:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.4 (1992:Winter/Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.7 (1992/1993:Winter). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.9 (1993:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.8 (1993:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.10 (1993/1994:Winter). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.13 (1994:Autumn). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.11 (1994:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: KFAT News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By National Union of Knitwear, Footwear and Apparel Trades. no.14 (1995:Spring). Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: EUR 12: The Europeans' Europe, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Commission of the European Communities. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.42:no.11 (1992:Nov.). Item is in German.
  - Item 3: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.43:no.6 (1993:June). Item is in German.
  - Item 4: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.43:no.7/8 (1993:July/Aug.). Item is in German.
  - Item 5: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.43:no.4 (1993:April). Item is in German.
  - Item 6: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.43:no.1 (1993:Jan.). Item is in German.
  - Item 7: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.44:no.11 (1994:Nov.). Item is in German.
  - Item 8: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.45:no.6 (1995:June). Item is in German.
  - Item 9: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.45:no.4 (1995:April). Item is in German.
  - Item 10: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.45:no.3 (1995:Mar.). Item is in German.
  - Item 11: Textil Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.45:no.1 (1995:Jan.). Item is in German.
- Box: 4, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Co-determination: Worker Participation in German Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By German Information Center. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Critical Issues: America, Germany, and the New Europe, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By Gregory F. Treverton;Barbara A. Bicksler. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Electoral Law, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By Inter Nationes. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: German Trade Union Federation, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By German Trade Union Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: German-American Trade Union Solidarity in the Struggle Against Fascism: 1933-1945, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By DGB (Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund); AFL-CIO. Report of DGB and AFL-CIO meeting in Dusseldorf, December 1984. Publication no.B-84 (1985:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: History, Aims, Tasks and Activities, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By Friedrich-Ebert-Stiftung. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Democracy in West Germany, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By Dr. Bernd Otto. Address to the International Industrial Democracy Conference, Adelaide, South Australia, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Programm der Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    By Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung. v.21:no.4 (1978:Nov.). Item is in German.
  - Item 9: The Law on Political parties, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Social Democracy and Development, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Chris Jecchins. Cover in English and Greek. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Soft Drink and Hard Labour; Guatemalan Workers Take on Coca-Cola, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    By Transport and General Workers Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Right To Organize In Guatemala: The Case Of Phillips-Van Heusen, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    By US/Guatemala Labor Education Project; International Labor Rights Education & Research Fund; Religious Task Force On Central America. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Haiti After the Coup: Sweatshop or Real Development?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker & Human Rights in Central America. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: No Greater Priority: Judicial Reform in Haiti, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By National Coalition For Haitian Refugees. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hungary On The Road To Reform: Challenges & Opportunities For U.S. Policy, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By The Atlantic Council of the United States. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Recent Trade Union Developments In Hungary, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By AFL-CIO International Affairs Department. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of ALF-CIO Delegation To Northern Ireland And To The Republic Of Ireland, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    By American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Histadrut, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    By The General Federation of Labour in Israel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Histadrut Means Service, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Labour In Israel, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Arabs in the Histadrut, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Accordo Integrativo Valsesiano, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    By Associazione Industriali Valsesia. Item is in Italian.
  - Item 2: CGIL today, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    By CGIL. Item is in English; Italian.
  - Item 3: Contratto Collettivo Nazionale Di Lavoro, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    By Associazione dell-Industria Laniera. Item is in Italian.
  - Item 4: Knowing The UIL, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    By Unione Italiana Del Lavoro. Item is in English; French; German; Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Fighting Exploitation on Famed Isle in Malaysia, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    By American Federation of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Organizing in Malaysia; A Model for Trade Union Cooperation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    By Asian-American Free Labor Institute. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: El Perfil del PRD, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    By Primer Congreso Nacional. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Running the Gauntlet: The Central American Journey in Mexico, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Committee for Refugees. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: International Bulletin: "19th of September, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    By National Garment Workers' Union. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Mexico Policy News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    By San Diego State University's Institute for Regional Studies of the Californias. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: SIDA: Manual de Trabajo para Capacitadores, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    By Secretaria de Salud. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Latin America Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    By Washington Office on Latin America. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 5, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Nicaragua Source Book, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By American Institute for Free Labor Development. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Estatutos de la Asociacion Magisterio Panameno Unido, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Box: 5, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Ang Pilipino, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Item is in Filipino; English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Across Frontiers: Spreading the Message of Free Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    By AFL-CIO Department of International Affairs. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Documents of the Second National Congress, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    By Coordinating Office Abroad of NSZZ Solidarnosc. Gdansk, 19-25 April 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: News Solidarnosc, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    By Coordinating Office Abroad of NSZZ Solidarnosc. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report to the AFL-CIO Executive Council: AFL-CIO President Lane Kirkland's Visit to Poland, Hungary, and Czechoslovakia: April 17 - May 2, 1990, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Box: 5, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: U.S. & Romania: Facing a Difficult Future Policy Recommendations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    By Task Force on Romania. Policy Paper. Item is in English.
- Box: 5, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Disinformation: Soviet Active Measures and Disinformation Forecast, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    By Institute for International Studies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of the AFL-CIO Subcommittee on Perestroika, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Box: 6, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations and Employment in Sweden, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Lennart Forseback. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Jobs Create Demand which Leads to More Jobs: Summary of Report to LO Congress 1986, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Swedish Trade Union Confederation. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Thai Workers Struggle for Democracy, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Turk-Is News Bulletin, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)